onehdwallpaper.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy – One HD Wallpaper Pictures Backgrounds FREE Download

## Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy for www.OneHDWallpaper.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by Clicking ( [Contact](https://onehdwallpaper.com/contact-us/) ).

At www.OneHDWallpaper.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.OneHDWallpaper.com and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.OneHDWallpaper.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### How we use collected information

One HD Wallpaper may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
– To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

www.OneHDWallpaper.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.OneHDWallpaper.com .  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit towww.OneHDWallpaper.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.OneHDWallpaper.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.OneHDWallpaper.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.OneHDWallpaper.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**HOW TO DOWNLOAD IMAGE IN FULL RESOLUTION:** Click on each image to view larger in light box, then right click on Picture and select “save image as …” to download Wallpapers into your desktop computer and laptop. If you are browsing website by handheld or touchscreen device, please tap on image for a while (3 seconds) and then select “save image as …” to download image to your mobile device.
